

ABOUT ME

Life is an ongoing learning process and after 10 successful years in Management, I felt the need to challenge myself and experiment a new career.

That's the reason why I joined an intensive training course at E2N School in order to become

CONTACT

+33 7 69 89 10 52

10 Cours Boufflet 60700 Pont Sainte Maxence FRANCE

franckyglatignypro@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- PHF
- Javascript
- Angular JS
- Symfony
- Bootstrap
- Méthode Agile
- SQL

FRANCKY GLATIGNY

EXPERIENCE

BNP Paribas CIB

Chief Happiness Officer

- Change management
- Treat every person as a human being who matters
- Ensure the basics of Maslow's principle are followed
- Give employees a voice
- Make sure the company values are demonstrated
- Support growth

Boulanger

Sales Team Manager

Apr 2017 to Oct 2017

Oct 2017 to Nov 2018

- Animate, motivate and grow the sales and merchandising team: recruitment, training, organization, monitoring, coaching
- Set, pilot and control individual and collective targets
- Analyze the different performance indicators; define and implement appropriate action plans
- Contributing to the overall store operation (optimizing and adapting human resources, guaranteeing the market and commercial environment of the universe)

Apple

Aug 2013 to Dec 2016

Customer Service Team Manager

- Maintain and improve individual performance levels of the team members to ensure targets are met
- Management of KPI's targets
- Plan and coordinate training, development and coaching.
- · Recruiting, seeking and sourcing profiles

EDUCATION

AWARDS

Professional title
"Web Developer / Mobile Web"
2019

"Apple Excellence Award" 2014

Intensive 6 months training course. Under graduate diploma. Nominated "Best manager of the year"